SOWMYA SANALA

Curriculum Vitae

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Konkordiastrasse 7 Berlin, 13595 Germany

PHONE

+49 17647005368

EMAIL

sowmyas.sanala@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

30/12/1992 India

NATIONALITY

Indian

SKILLS

Problem Solving Skills

Windows versions, Mac

Github, Jira, Confluence

Zephyr, Mantis bug tracker

Selenium with Java

Appium

Testng Framework

Extent Reports

PROFILE

Quality Assurance Engineer with 6 years of work experience in Agile methodology. Ability to learn quickly, often in high pressure situations, in order to fully understand the new product, platform or any mixture of two. Looking for a challenging and multicultural work environment where I can enhance my skills.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Quality Assurance Enginnering, Cortado Holding AG GmbH

Berlin

Dec 2019 — Oct 2023

- Design, develop, and execute test plans for mobile application testing.
- · Closely working with the development team
- Expand the role and scope of mobile device testing to include user acceptance testing
- Perform objective code analysis to find and fix bugs in mobile applications
- Review mobile device compatibility and report any potential issues to management
- Ensure quality assurance, successful completion of project goals, and adherence to project schedules.
- Knowledge of application testing, QA methodologies and frameworks
- · Knowledge of mobile testing tools and resources

Quality Analyst, Cognizant

India Hyderabad

Mar 2017 — Feb 2019

- Understanding the software requirement specifications and identifying the required test scenarios for the project.
- · Preparing the test cases and executing them manually.
- Working with the developers and the project support teams for identifying \square the issues and fixing the bugs.
- Review User Interfaces for consistency, functionality and interact with Project Manager during sprint planning.
- Involved in Functional, Integration, Regression & Compatibility Testing techniques.

Cucumber BDD Framework

Process Associate, Just Dial Private Limited India Hyderabad

Jan 2015 — Nov 2016

• Interacting with clients and providing product demos. Closing deals and preparing online business documentation.

vith clients in resolving their queries. Planning and or on-boarding team members.

tegist, Intelenet Global Services India Hyderabad b 2017

e marketing strategies using all necessary tools. Analyze web traπıc metrics and suggest solutions to boost web presence.

• Identify advertising needs and build a strong client base through social media interaction.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, India.

India

Aug 2010 — Jun 2014

Thesis: Privacy preserving data sharing with anonymous id assignment. Aurora's Scientific Technological & Research Academy, India.